<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Be True</title>
	<atom:link href="http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php</link>
	<description>Thank you for reading fresh news</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 21:45:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>David Oyelowo joins Oprah Winfrey&#8217;s town hall special to talk about police brutality</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Без рубрики]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)Oprah Winfrey&#8217;s town hall on race featured a deep discussion with actor and director David Oyelowo, who revealed he&#8217;s been [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)Oprah Winfrey&#8217;s town hall on race featured a deep discussion with actor and director David Oyelowo, who revealed he&#8217;s been crying for two weeks over the civil unrest in America, and said he&#8217;s had to have tough conversations about police brutality with his young son.</p>
<p>In &#8220;OWN Spotlight: Where Do We Go From Here,&#8221; the actor, who portrayed the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. in &#8220;Selma,&#8221; explains that because he is of Nigerian descent, he has dealt with racism throughout his life.<br />
He admits to mistakes he&#8217;s made, such as thinking racism was a thing of &#8220;the past,&#8221; and advising his son to not get &#8220;confrontational&#8221; with police officers if ever in a situation with them.<br />
Oyelowo said that when he saw that George Floyd wasn&#8217;t resisting arrest while being taken into custody by Minneapolis police, he realized the problem of police brutality is even worse than he believed.<br />
&#8220;I had made the mistake of thinking that things would be different for my son. I say mistake because I had watched things progress in some ways. And then the knee on the neck is so symbolic of so much,&#8221; he said. &#8220;It&#8217;s something I didn&#8217;t realize that I had internalized in a way that makes it difficult for me to function. I didn&#8217;t realize how deep the wounds were. I have spent so much of the last two weeks crying.&#8221;<br />
He continued: &#8220;Those conversations are already emasculating to basically say, forget about justice in an interaction with the police.&#8221;<br />
&#8221; allowfullscreen><br />
Winfrey said she understood, telling viewers that&#8217;s a conversation many black parents have with their children. &#8220;Yeah. And for everybody who&#8217;s watching who is not black, that is the conversation, that is the talk that every black parent has had to have with their children, particularly their sons,&#8221; she said.<br />
Winfrey also spoke with director Ava DuVernay, Atlanta Mayor Keisha Lance Bottoms and Stacey Abrams, along with other leaders and activists.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Julia Roberts, Gwyneth Paltrow giving social media accounts over to black voices for #ShareTheMicNow</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Julia Roberts and Gwyneth Paltrow are turning their social media accounts over to black women. (CNN)&#8221;When the world listens to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Julia Roberts and Gwyneth Paltrow are turning their social media accounts over to black women.<br />
(CNN)&#8221;When the world listens to women, it listens to white women.&#8221;</p>
<p>That is part of the mission statement behind the social media campaign #ShareTheMicNow.<br />
On Wednesday, several prominent white women including Julia Roberts, Gwyneth Paltrow, Ashley Judd and Kourtney Kardashian are turning their social media accounts over to black activists, celebrities and content creators for the day.<br />
The Instagram campaign was conceived by Endeavor chief marketing officer Bozoma Saint John, author/podcast host Luvvie Ajayi Jones, author/Together Rising founder Glennon Doyle and Alice + Olivia founder Stacey Bendet.</p>
<p>According to a press release, the campaign seeks &#8220;to magnify Black women and the important work that they&#8217;re doing in order to catalyze the change that will only come when we truly hear each other&#8217;s voices.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;For far too long, Black women&#8217;s voices have gone unheard, even though they&#8217;ve been using their voices loudly for centuries to enact change,&#8221; the mission statement reads. &#8220;Today, more than ever, it is NECESSARY that we create a unifying action to center Black women&#8217;s lives, stories, and calls to action. We need to listen to Black women.&#8221;<br />
#ShareTheMicNow is the latest attempt to #amplifyblackvoices as the death of George Floyd while in the custody of Minneapolis police has resulted in protests and much conversation about race.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rihanna, Ariana Grande and more artists sign open letter calling for police reform in New York</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 16:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)Some of the biggest names in the music industry are joining the call for reform of policing in New York. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)Some of the biggest names in the music industry are joining the call for reform of policing in New York.</p>
<p>Rihanna, Ariana Grande, Billie Eilish, Justin Bieber, Post Malone, Meek Mill, the Jonas Brothers and many more signed an open letter on Monday, asking New York legislators to repeal section 50-A of New York State&#8217;s Civil Rights Law.<br />
New York legislators expected to pass bills targeting police misconduct<br />
New York legislators expected to pass bills targeting police misconduct<br />
The statute currently keeps police personnel files confidential and basically out of the public&#8217;s reach.<br />
&#8220;We mourn the killing of George Floyd and the unnecessary loss of so many black lives before his. We must hold accountable those who violate the oath to protect and serve, and find justice for those who are victim to their violence,&#8221; the open letter reads in part.<br />
&#8220;An indispensable step is having access to disciplinary records of law enforcement officers. New York statute 50-A blocks that full transparency, shielding a history of police misconduct from public scrutiny, making it harder to seek justice and bring about reform. It must be repealed immediately.&#8221;<br />
The letter is directed at Gov. Andrew Cuomo, New York Senate Majority Leader Andrea Stewart-Cousins and Assembly Speaker Carl Heastie. The petition and open letter comes in the wake of George Floyd&#8217;s death in Minneapolis after former police officer Derek Chauvin pressed his knee on Floyd&#8217;s neck for nearly nine minutes.<br />
George Floyd protests have made police reform the consensus position<br />
George Floyd protests have made police reform the consensus position<br />
The letter goes on to state, &#8220;It is not enough to chip away at 50-A; this boulder in the path of justice has stood in the way for far too long and must be crushed entirely.<br />
New York&#8217;s Legislature is poised to take action on a police reform package that includes repealing section 50-A.<br />
On Tuesday, Cuomo said there is a need for real discussion on how to &#8220;reinvent and reimagine policing for a new generation and a new society.&#8221; He noted the discussion is a &#8220;long time coming and long overdue.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
